babyhopes.com 2014-11-29

# Privacy and Security Policy babyhopes

Privacy and Security Statement

Effective August 1, 2008 

Our Commitment To Privacy: 

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

* * *

The Information We Collect: 

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the BabyHopes.com website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: 

Name   
Address   
Email address   
Phone number   
Credit/Debit Card Information 

On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you order a gift online and want it sent directly to the recipient, you will need to submit the recipient's address. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected are: 

Name   
Address   
Phone Number 

Our shopping cart uses cookies to keep track of your order. If you return in 30 days, your name and address will be automatically entered into the forms. No other information will be stored. 

Our article area serves advertisements from Google Adsense.

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. 
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to the users users of this site based on their visit to this sites and other sites on the Internet. 
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

* * *

The Way We Use Information:

We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. 

We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. 

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. 

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals. 

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. 

* * *

Our Commitment To Data Security: 

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

The online transactions at BabyHopes.com are handled with industry-standard SSL encryption. It's easy to tell when you are protected by encryption -- the lock or key at the bottom of your browser changes color or is no longer broken. This may vary depending on your browser. If you see https:// instead of http:// at the top of the browser, this also means that what you are doing is being encrypted.

All credit card numbers are encrypted and stored in the secure server until the transaction has been authorised. Once authorised, the encrypted credit card number is totally erased from the server. 

* * *

Our Commitment To Children's Privacy:   
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13. 

* * *

How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information:

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by [contacting us](http://www.earthsmagic.com/support-center/) via our contact form. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. 

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. 

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

* * *

How To Contact Us:   
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please contact us via our [contact form](http://www.earthsmagic.com/support-center/).
